

DAVID GOMES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hi, I'm David, an aspiring software developer with 25 years of age.

I started to learn how to program about 2 years ago when joined 42 and now I feel ready to do the step up in the career and start professionally. I do not seek competitive environments, I want to continue learning and also dream of seeing my contributions in the world.

In these past years I've learned to code in C and C++, Shell scripting for tests and fun, Docker containerization, Threads and Processes, Bash (We actually had a project that required to recreate it), Git is mandatory in the day-to-day life, Graphical Libraries and Web development. My favorite languages are C and C++ at the moment, and I would love to keep working with them, but I can learn any language rather quickly.

EDUCATION

2021 - Present

42 Lisboa

Finishing Common Core

2017 - 2020

Universidade da Beira Interior

BSc in Architecture (DNF)

LANGUAGES

Portuguese: Native

English: Fluent

Spanish: Moderate

CONTACTS

+351 927 794 191

davidmdg98@hotmail.com

Guarda, Portugal

EXPERIENCES

Factory Quality Verifier

Coficab Cable Company, 2020 - 2021

- I was a versatile member in the quality department having worked in every role there was.
- My main job at the factory was to monitor multiple production lines, identifying problems early and keeping the machines from producing not eligible cable for the clients, and preventing the loss of money and waste of resources.
- The constant cable production made me learn how to best manage my time and also deal with work stress.

Volunteer

Clube Escape Livre, 2020-2022

I volunteered at Clube Escape Livre in my free time due to my love for cars and this gave me the opportunity to drive and see cars up close that I might have not the chance to otherwise.

Also helped making the routes for the tours, checkpointed tours and delivered and photographed cars.

Visit my personal web CV with some links to my socials and projects:

